(joyful guitar music)
♪ Lord Almighty ♪
♪ I feel my temperature rising ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Higher and higher ♪
♪ It's burning through to my soul ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Girl, girl, girl, girl ♪
♪ You're gonna set me on fire ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ My brain is flamin' ♪
♪ I don't know which way to go ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song of a choir ♪
♪ You light my morning sky ♪
♪ Burning love ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I feel my temperature rising ♪
♪ Rising, rising, rising ♪
♪ Help me, I'm flamin' ♪
♪ I must be a hundred and nine ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Burnin', burnin' ♪
♪ Burnin' and nothing can cool me ♪
♪ Cool me, cool me, cool me ♪
♪ I just might turn into smoke ♪
♪ But I feel fine ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song of a choir ♪
♪ And you light my morning sky ♪
♪ Burning love ♪
- [Choir] ♪ Burning love ♪
(joyful guitar music continues)
♪ Burning love ♪
♪ ♪ Burning love ♪
♪ It's coming closer ♪
♪ The flames are now reaching my body ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Please, won't you help me ♪
♪ I feel like I'm slipping away ♪
♪ It's hard to breathe ♪
♪ And my chest is a-heavin' ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Lord Almighty ♪
♪ I'm burning a hole where I lay ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song of a choir ♪
♪ And you light my morning sky ♪
♪ Burning love ♪
♪ Just a hunk ♪
♪ A hunk of burning love ♪
♪ I'm just a hunk ♪
(audience cheering)